Oh, they should. I own the place.
How could you want to raise children
in a city like this?
-Well, I was raised here. I turned out okay.
-Is Wayne Manor in the city limits?
Is--? Heh-heh.
The Palisades? Sure.
You know, as our new DA, you might wanna
figure out where your jurisdiction ends.
I'm talking about the kind of city
that idolizes a masked vigilante.
Gotham City is proud of an ordinary citizen
standing up for what's right.
Gotham needs heroes like you,
elected officials...
-...not a man who thinks he's above the law.
-Who appointed the Batman?
We did. All of us who stood by
and let scum take control of our city.
But this is a democracy, Harvey.
When their enemies were at the gates...
...the Romans would suspend democracy
and appoint one man to protect the city.
It wasn't considered an honor,
it was a public service.
Harvey, the last man that they appointed to
protect the republic was named Caesar...
-...and he never gave up his power.
-Okay, fine.
You either die a hero...
...or you live long enough
to see yourself become the villain.
Like...